// NextQuizData.js

const nextQuizData = [
    {
        question: "1) What does HTML stand for?",
        options: [
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "High Tech Markup Language",
            "Hyperlink and Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language"
        ],
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
        question: "2) Which CSS property is used to change the text color of an element?",
        options: [
            "color",
            "text-color",
            "font-color",
            "change-color"
        ],
        answer: "color"
    },
    {
        question: "3) What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'script.js'?",
        options: [
            "<script src='script.js'>",
            "<script href='script.js'>",
            "<script ref='script.js'>",
            "<script name='script.js'>"
        ],
        answer: "<script src='script.js'>"
    },
    {
        question: "4) If we want to set the style for just one element, which css selector will we use?",
        options: [
            "id",
            "text",
            "class",
            "name"
        ],
        answer: "id"
    },
    {
        question: "5) The Head tag is used for?",
        options: [
            "Writing CSS styles",
            "Writing Javascript",
            "Including CSS and JS files",
            "All the answers are true"
        ],
        answer: "All the answers are true"
    },
    {
        question: "6) Which element has very similar properties to the DIV element?",
        options: [
            "strong",
            "span",
            "table",
            "All the answers are true"
        ],
        answer: "span"
    },
    {
        question: "7) If button is clicked which event handler is used?",
        options: [
            "OnSubmit()",
            "OnLoad()",
            "IsPostBack()",
            "Onclick()"
        ],
        answer: "Onclick()"
    },
    {
        question: "8) Which Of The Dialog Box Display a Message And a Data Entry Field?",
        options: [
            "Alert()",
            "Prompt()",
            "Confirm()",
            "Msg()"
        ],
        answer: "Prompt()"
    },
    {
        question: "9) Which of the following object is the main entry point to all client-side JavaScript features and APIs?",
        options: [
            "Position",
            "Window",
            "Standard",
            "Location"
        ],
        answer: "Window"
    },
    {
        question: "10) To create a link to an anchor, you use which property in a tag",
        options: [
            "Name",
            "Tag",
            "Link",
            "Href"
        ],
        answer: "Href"
    },

];

export default nextQuizData;
